smartserve.ca 2018-08-12

# Privacy Policy – Smart Serve Ontario

Last Updated:  March 2011

### Privacy Policy

Smart Serve Ontario (“Smart Serve”) has created this privacy statement (“Statement”) in order to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of the customers of Smart Serve’s products and services (“Customers”) and other persons visiting the Smart Serve Website (“Visitors”). Because we gather important information from our Customers and Visitors, we have established this Statement as a means to communicate our information gathering and dissemination practices.

By using the Website, you signify your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Statement. We reserve the right to change this Statement at any time without notice to you. Your continued use of the Website subsequent to any changes to this Statement will signify that you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with the changed Statement in effect at the time you use the Website. If you do not accept the change, stop using the Website. When you visit the Website, you should check the “Last Updated” date at the top of this Statement and review any changes made. We encourage you to periodically review this Statement to be aware of changes made.

Smart Serve collects information from our Visitors and Customers at several different points on our Website so that we can inform you about our products based on the preferences you have identified. This way, we can send you relevant information that meets your needs and ensure that your visit to our site is quick, easy and productive.

Smart Serve is the sole owner of the information collected on this Website. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this Statement.

**Collected Information**

To accurately setup new customer accounts, we require Customers to provide us with contact information for the Customer, such as their date of birth, name, address, phone number, and e-mail address.

Smart Serve uses the information that we collect to set up the Smart Serve application for Customers, to manage Customers’ accounts, to communicate with Customers about training and other services. We may also use the information we collect to contact Customers to provide information about Smart Serve and new products or services we think may be of interest or use to the Customer or to discuss the Customer’s interest in our company or support for our products. Customers can opt out of receiving these communications by replying to them at the time they are distributed or at any time by e-mailing [privacy@smartserve.ca](mailto:privacy@smartserve.ca). Customers cannot, however, opt out of audit notifications and other communications required to administer the service provided by Smart Serve.

Customers of the Smart Serve application will be using the Smart Serve application to host their data and information (“Data”). Customer Data may at times be viewed or accessed by authorized Smart Serve employees, contractors and representatives only for the purposes of ensuring the proper operation and provision of the Smart Serve application, such as resolving a technical problem or support issue, or for investigating and addressing a suspected violation of the Terms of Use. Smart Serve will not review, share, distribute, print, or reference any such Data, except as provided in this Statement, the Smart Serve Terms of Use, or as may be required by law. Of course, Customers are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of their user registration and password, and you can and should take steps to do so.

Smart Serve may provide Visitor and Customer personal information and Customer Data to third parties that provide services to Smart Serve for the Website under contract with Smart Serve (“Suppliers”), such as managing Visitor and Customer information collected by Smart Serve and activity across the Smart Serve Website, and to host information and Data, but these parties are not permitted to use the information or Data for their own purposes. We do not distribute to or share personal information, Data or our Customer or Visitor lists with third parties except as described in this Statement, or as may be required by law.

**Cookies**

When you interact with the Smart Serve Website, we strive to make that experience easy and meaningful. When you come to our Website, our Web server sends a cookie to your computer. Cookies are files that Web browsers place on a computer’s hard drive and are used to tell us whether Customers and Visitors have visited the Site previously. They do not identify you personally; they merely recognize your browser.

Smart Serve uses cookies to track or record information about our Website Visitors. Visitors who disable their Web browsers’ ability to accept cookies will be able to browse the Smart Serve Website but may not be able to successfully register for training items and other features offered by Smart Serve.

For Customers, Smart Serve uses cookies containing encrypted information to allow the Smart Serve application to uniquely identify you while you are logged in. This information allows Smart Serve to process your online transactions and requests. Cookies help us make sure you are who you say you are after you’ve logged in and are required in order to use the Smart Serve application.

**Third Party Sites**

The Smart Serve Website contains links to other Web sites. Smart Serve is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other Web sites. Customers and Visitors must check the policy statement of these others Web sites to understand their policies. Customers and Visitors who access a linked site may be disclosing their private information. It is your responsibility to keep such information private and confidential.

**Security**

To keep transactions and your personal information secure, the Smart Serve Website uses the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol, which electronically encrypts any information you send to us. The encryption process protects information such as your credit card number, billing and shipping information by scrambling the data before it is sent to us from your computer.

It is important for you to be protected against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**Retention of Information**

Smart Serve is obliged to maintain Customer information with respect to training records, including access history and test results, for law enforcement purposes. Where possible, Smart Serve will not retain information longer than is necessary.

Customers may request that information with respect to such Customer that is not required to be retained for law enforcement or similar purposes be deleted by sending an email to [privacy@smartserve.ca](mailto:privacy@smartserve.ca).

Financial information with respect to Customers is not retained longer than eighteen (18) months from the date of the purchase of Smart Serve services. On or before the date that is eighteen (18) months from the purchase of Smart Serve services, Smart Serve will cause such financial information to be deleted.

**Correcting & Updating Your Information**

Website Visitors can update their contact information or opt-out of receiving further communications by sending an email to [info@smartserve.ca](mailto:info@smartserve.ca). In your email, please specify the exact communications you would like to no longer receive.

Visitors and Customers may request access to personal information collected by Smart Serve by sending an email to [privacy@smartserve.ca](mailto:privacy@smartserve.ca). Subject to certain exceptions and limitations prescribed by law, you will be given access to your personal information within a reasonable time and will be entitled to challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and have it amended as appropriate.

**Additional Information**

Questions regarding this Statement or the practices of the Smart Serve Website and Smart Serve application should be directed to Smart Serve’s privacy officer at [privacy@smartserve.ca](mailto:privacy@smartserve.ca).
